Guide to the Postcards of female and male impersonators and cross-dressing, circa 1900-1930.
Postcards of female and male impersonators and cross-dressing,
- Spain (Box 2)
  - Music Hall, Theater, and Film (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Carbonell-Lopez, 1900; 232; 14 x 9 cm; Applied color. Undivided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 6)
      Two male impersonators dressed in folk-dance suits against studio backdrop of café.
      Madrid, Spain
- United Kingdom (Box 2)
  - Music Hall, Theater, and Film (Box 2)
    - Miss Sybil Arnudale, 1909; 235; Bromochrom; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Male impersonator dressed as 18th-century male aristocrat.
      Arnudale, Sybil
    - Mr. Wilkie Bard, 1910; 236; Rotary Photo, E.C.; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Bard, Wilkie
    - Female impersonator as Edwardian bride, 1910; 237; 14 x 9 cm; Signed. Divided verso. (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Benson, Ally
    - Bessie Bonehill, 1904; 238; 14 x 9 cm; Inscribed. Divided verso. (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Bonehill, Bessie
    - Mr. Herbert Campbell, 1903; 239; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Campbell, Herbert
    - Baroness and Baron, Cinderella, Brixton Theatre, 1910; 240; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Conway, Tom
      French, George
    - Miss Zena Dare as Duc de Richelieu in The Dashing Little Duke, 1910; 241; Rotary Photo, E.C.; Foulsham and Banfield; 14 x 9 cm; Inscribed. Divided verso. (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Dare, Zena
    - Miss Zena Dare in Peter Pan, 1906; 242; Davidson Brothers; 14 x 9 cm; Inscribed. Divided verso. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Fred Emney, 1910; 243; Gray, Campbell; 14 x 9 cm; Signed. Divided verso. (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Emeny, Fred, Sr.
    - Maudie Goodman, 1910; 244; Imperial Publishing Co.; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Goodman, Maudie
      Longton, England
    - "Tommie" Hunter, 1931; 245; Foster and Harwood; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Hunter, Tommie
      Brighton, England
    - Miss Hetty King, 1909; 246; Rotary Photo; 14 x 9 cm; Signed. Divided verso. (Box 2, Folder 9)
      King wearing day suit and top hat.
      King, Hetty
    - Miss Hetty King, 1907; 247; Whitlock; Philco Publishing Co.; 14 x 9 cm; Signed and inscribed. Divided verso. (Box 2, Folder 9)
      King wearing suit and boater hat.
    - Miss Hettie King, 1905; 248; Whitlock; Rotary Photo; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Miss Hetty King, 1910; 249; Philco Publishing Co.; 14 x 9 cm; Inscribed. Divided verso. (Box 2, Folder 9)
      King wearing braided coat and cap with chin strap.
    - Miss Hetty King, 1910; 250; Bamber, J.P.; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 9)
      King dressed as military officer.
      Blackpool, United Kingdom
    - Hetty King, 1906; 251; Brown, R.; Philco Publishing Co.; 14 x 9 cm; Inscribed. Divided verso. (Box 2, Folder 9)
      King dressed as sailor with pipe.
    - Miss Hetty King says when you go home - follow the tram lines., 1910; 252; Tear, Herbert; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Offset lithographs
    - Lane? "La Maxixe.", 1906; 253; Hana Studios Ltd.; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Miss Rita Leggiero as "Little Hal" in "A White Man", 1908; 254; Rotary Photo, E.C.; Foulsham and Banfield; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 10)
      Promotional postcard for the 1908 London production of A White Man at the Lyric Theatre.
      Leggiero, Rita
    - Miss Edna May, 1906; 255; Philco Publishing Co.; W. and D. Downey; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 10)
      May, Edna (1878-1948)
    - Miss Gertie Millar, 1905; 256; Rotary Photo, E.C.; Foulsham and Banfield; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 10)
      Promotional postcard for a 1905 London musical The Spring Chicken.
      Millar, Gertie (1879-1952)
    - Miss Evelyn Millard "Robin Hood", 1907; 257; Rotary Photo, E.C.; Foulsham and Banfield; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 10)
      Millard, Evelyn (1869-1941)
    - Female impersonators Ben and Jim Obo, 1920; 258; Dyche; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. Signed. (Box 2, Folder 10)
      Obo, Ben
      Obo, Jim
      Birmingham, England
    - Molly Poulton, 1900; 259; Hana Photo; 14 x 9 cm; Undivided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 10)
      Poulton dressed in white bow tie and top hat.
      Poulton, Molly
    - Molly Poulton, 1900; 260; Hana Photo; 14 x 9 cm; Undivided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Mr. Harry Randall, 1905; 261; Rotary Photo, E.C.; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 11)
      Randall, Harry or Randall, Thomas William (1857-1932)
    - Mr. Harry Randall, 1907; 262; Rotary Photo, E.C.; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Miss Gabrielle Ray, 1910; 263; Rotary Photo, E.C.; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 11)
      Ray dressed as sailor.
      Ray, Gabrielle or Cook, Gabriell Elizabeth Clifford (1883-1973)
    - Mr. George Robey, 1910; 264; Rotary Photo, E.C.; Foulsham and Banfield; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 11)
      Robey, George or Wade, Sir George Edward (1869-1954)
    - Mr. Fred Spencer, 1905; 265; J. White and Son; 14 x 9 cm; Signed. Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 11)
      Spencer, Fred
      Littlehampton, England
    - Vesta Tilley, 1903; 266; Rotary Photo, E.C.; Brown, Barnes and Bell; 14 x 9 cm; Signed. Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 12)
      Tilley wearing top hat and carrying walking stick.
      Tilley, Vesta or Powles, Matilda Alice (1864-1952)
    - Miss Vesta Tilley, 1903; 267; Rapid Photo Co.; Brown, Barnes and Bell; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Miss Vesta Tilley, 1906; 268; Rotary Photo, E.C.; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Miss Vesta Tilley, 1905; 269; Philco Publishing Co.; 14 x 9 cm; Three images recto. Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Miss Vesta Tilley, 1906; 270; J. Beagles and Co.; 14 x 9 cm; The figure has applied color and the background is overlaid with gold leaf. Divided verso, inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Miss Vesta Tilley, 1905; 271; Rapid Photo Co.; Brown, Barnes and Bell; 14 x 9 cm; Applied color. Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Miss Vesta Tilley, 1908; 272; Philco Publishing Co.; 14 x 9 cm; Two images recto. Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Vesta Tilley, 1905; 273; Philco Publishing Co.; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 13)
      Tilley sitting at a writing desk.
    - Miss Vesta Tilley, 1904; 274; Rotary Photo, E.C.; Brown, Barnes and Bell; 14 x 9 cm; Applied color. Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 13)
      Tilley dressed as a sailor.
    - Miss Vesta Tilley, 1905; 275; Rotary Photo, E.C.; James Bacon and Sons; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Vesta Tilley, 1910; 276; Woolstone Brothers; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 13)
      Part of the Milton "Glossette" series.
    - Vesta Tilley, 1910; 277; Philco Publishing Co.; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Vesta Tilley, 1915; 278; Philco Publishing Co.; 14 x 9 cm; Undivided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 13)
      Tilley dressed as a soldier.
    - Miss Vesta Tilley in Khaki, 1915; 279; David Allen and Sons; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 13)
      Sale of these postcards was intended for donation to the War Relief Funds.
    - Miss Vesta Tilley, 1910; 280; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 13)
      Tilley in day gown climbing out of town car. Part of "The Star Series" by G.D. and D., London
    - Jack Whymont, 1920; 281; King and Wilson; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 14)
      Whymont, Jack
      Bognor, England
    - Georgie Wood as Vesta Tilley, 1905; 282; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 14)
      Wood, George (1894-1979)
    - Winifred Ward, 1905; 283; 14 x 9 cm; Signed. Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 14)
      Ward, Winifred
    - Miss Winifred Ward, 1910; 284; Rotary Photo, E.C.; Foulsham and Banfield; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Miss Winifred Ward, "Jack Horner" Pantomime, Princess Theatre, Bristol, 1910; 285; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Mr. Huntley Wright in "A Country Girl", 1910; 286; Eillis and Walery; J. Beagles and Co.; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 14)
      Wright, Huntley (1868-1941)
    - Mr. Huntley Wright, 1910; 287; Eillis and Walery; J. Beagles and Co.; 14 x 4.8 cm; Bookmark format postcard. (Box 2, Folder 14)
      Same image as postcard 286.
    - Mr. Huntley Wright, 1910; 288; Eillis and Walery; J. Beagles and Co.; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - My Lady Molly Act I, 1903; 289; J. Beagles and Co.; 9 x 14 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Humor (Box 2)
    - O, du lieber Augustin, 1905; 362; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Sweet sixteen and never been kissed, 1905; 363; Bamforth and Co.; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 29)
      Holmfirth, England
      New York, New York, United States
    - I'm not so dispoged, 1910; 364; C.W. Faulkner and Co.; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 29)
      Photomechanical prints
    - Men and male impersonators in work clothes, 1910; 365; 9 x 14 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Male and female impersonators in day wear, 1905; 366; 9 x 14 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Male impersonator in suit and fedora, 1910; 367; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Male impersonators in suits on porch, 1903; 368; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Two male impersonators, 1905; 369; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Male impersonators playing fiddles, 1905; 370; 9 x 14 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Man and male impersonator in patriotic costumes, 1920; 371; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Male impersonators with rakes and pitchforks by hay mounds, 1914; 372; 9 x 14 cm; Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Women and male impersonators as wedding party, 1910; 373; 9 x 14 cm; Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Male impersonators smoking cigars, 1910; 374; 9 x 14 cm; Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Male impersonators in front of stack of lumber, 1910; 375; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Male impersonators dressed as a soldier and a sailor, 1915; 376; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Two male impersonators and one female impersonator, 1910; 377; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Has any one seen Kelly? I've got his job, 1910; 378; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 30)
      Male impersonator
    - Waiting for the males, 1907; 379; Eckstone, C.; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Woman with two male impersonators as suitors, 1910; 380; Westbrook, Jessie; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 30)
      Defiance, Iowa
- Germany (Box 2)
  - Troops and POW shows, WWI (Box 2)
    - Ca sent la fuite!! Revue de A. Delarue, 1918; 294; 9 x 14 cm; Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 17)
      POW theatrical. Markings includes censor's clearance stamp.
      Gustrow, Germany
    - Dulmen Theatre du camp. "Le Veilleur de Nuit." (1 acte), 1915; 295; 9 x 14 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 17)
      Production of 1911 play by Sacha Guitry by French prisoners at the Dulmen POW camp in North Rhine - Westphalia.
    - The English Theatre, 1915; 296; Tellgman, Hans; 14 x 9 cm; Blank verso. (Box 2, Folder 17)
      POW theatrical by prisonors of camp in Langensalza, Germany. Captions in Frnech, English and Russian.
      Langensalza, Germany
    - The English Theatre, 1915; 297; Tellgman, Hans; 9 x 14 cm; Blank verso. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - The English Theatre, 1915; 298; Tellgman, Hans; 14 x 9 cm; Blank verso. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - The French Theatre, 1915; 299; Tellgman, Hans; 9 x 14 cm; Blank verso. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - The French Theatre, 1915; 300; Tellgman, Hans; 9 x 14 cm; Blank verso. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - The French Theatre, 1915; 301; Tellgman, Hans; 9 x 14 cm; Blank verso. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - La Fin Tragique, 1915; 302; 9 x 14 cm (Box 2, Folder 18)
      Printed verso includes lines for permited information, limited to name and address of sender and recipient.
      Konigsbruck, Germany
    - English Theater, Lager Cottbus. Miss Russon, J.A. Butler, 1915; 303; Tharan, Paul; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. (Box 2, Folder 18)
      POW theatrical. No inscription.
      Cottbus, Germany
    - Kriegsgef, Lager Cottbus. Russ. Theater, 1915; 304; Tharan, Paul; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. (Box 2, Folder 18)
      POW theatrical. Inscribed.
    - Russ Theater, Lager Cottbus, 1915; 305; Tharan, Paul; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - English Theater, 1915; 306; Tharan, Paul; 9 x 14 cm; Divided verso. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Theatre francais, groupe d'artists, 1918; 307; Magenmiller, Ilse; 9 x 14 cm; Divided verso. (Box 2, Folder 18)
      Ingolstadt, Germany
    - La Valse de Soissons, 1915; 308; Muller, Walter; 9 x 14 cm; Divided verso. (Box 2, Folder 18)
      Paderborn, Germany
    - English POW theatrical, 1915; 309; Skowranek, Otto; 9 x 14 cm; Divided verso. (Box 2, Folder 18)
      Berlin, Germany
  - Gallant (Box 2)
    - Officer and girl, 1910; 346; Neue Photographische Gesellschaft; 14 x 9 cm; Applied color. Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Humor (Box 2)
    - Der Marketendersepple, 1903; 258; Sauter, Ernst; 9 x 14 cm; Undivided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 26)
      Schonach, Germany
    - Peasant couple, 1906; 259; 9 x 14 cm; Applied color. Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 26)
- United States (Box 2)
  - Music Hall, Theater and Film (Box 2)
    - Dolores Costello of the Vitagraph Players, 1911; 290; Vitagraph Company of America; 14 x 9 cm; Blank verso. (Box 2, Folder 15)
      Costello dressed as a sailor.
      Costello, Dolores (1903-1979)
      Brooklyn, New York
    - Chinese Actor impersonating a female character, Chinese Theatre, 623 Jackosn Street, San Francisco, 1906; 291; 14 x 9 cm; Undivided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 15)
      San Francisco, California
- Italy (Box 2)
  - Humor (Box 2)
    - Male impersonator as soldier, 1917; 360; 14 x 9 cm; Applied color. Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Romania (Box 2)
  - Humor (Box 2)
    - Young male impersonator as sailor, 1924; 361; Baraschy; 14 x 9 cm; Toned. Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 28)
      Bucharest, Romania